[SALES (855) 661-9022](tel:(855) 661-9022)[SUPPORT (888) 534‑1711](tel:(888) 534%E2%80%911711)

* Products
* Solutions

* Resources

Updated March 01, 2024

Privacy Policy
==============

Thank you for visiting www.justworks.com. Justworks, Inc. (“Company”) is committed to treating the personal and corporate information of our users with respect and sensitivity. Our privacy commitment is described in this Privacy Policy.

As our services evolve and we perceive the need or desirability of using information collected in other ways, we may from time to time amend this Privacy Policy. We post the effective date of our Privacy Policy on our website (“Site”).

For the Canadian Privacy Policy, click [here](https://justworks.com/privacy-policy-canada).

Contents

Application of This Privacy Policy: This Privacy Policy applies to your use of (regardless of means of access) any of the current set of products from Company, collectively referred to as “Company Products”, such as our website ([www.justworks.com](https://justworks.com/)). The Company Products are owned and provided by Company.

You can access through applications on Devices. A “Device” is any computer used to access the Company Products, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic Device.

Company Products can enable you to use applications developed by third parties, individually and collectively referred to as “Third Party Apps” on a Device, such as an Android app on a Device running either the Microsoft Windows, Apple OS X or Linux operating systems.

General Information
-------------------

We believe that you have the right to understand how your information is stored and used. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites although we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites.

Information You Provide Us
--------------------------

In general, you can visit [www.justworks.com](https://justworks.com/) without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. If you wish to obtain information about our products or services you can contact us. We may collect your name, company name, email address, and street address along with other information you may choose to submit, as part of the inquiry process (“Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII”). When you register for a Company account, we collect some PII, which may include your name, company name, email address, telephone number, street address, taxpayer and immigration information, payroll, insurance and banking information. You may be asked to choose log-in Information, such as your email address and a password which will be used to access your account.

By providing your PII to us, you explicitly agree to our collection and use of such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Bank credentials submitted as part of Justworks' real-time payment verification program are subject to provisions of the privacy policy available at [this link](https://plaid.com/legal/).

Information Automatically Collected
-----------------------------------

We (or our service providers acting on our behalf) may collect Information about the Company Products that you use and how you use them. This information includes information that may identify you as well as statistical information (“Analytics”) that does not identify you. Some Analytics may be correlated with your PII. Usage Information may include:

### A. DEVICE INFORMATION

We may collect Device-specific Information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique Device identifiers and mobile network Information including phone number). We may associate your Device identifiers or phone number with your Company Account.

#### B. LOG INFORMATION

When you use Company Products, we may automatically record or log Information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Company Products. This may include:

* The Device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address;
    
* Identification numbers associated with your Devices;
    
* Device event Information such as crashes, system activity and hardware settings;
    
* Locale preferences;
    
* Application activity such as app upload, app download, app installation, app uninstallation, app start, app play duration, app stop, app crashes, app network activity and app resource consumption;
    
* Date and time stamps associated with transactions;
    
* System configuration Information;
    
* Metadata concerning your Android apps; and
    
* Other interactions with the Company Products.

Protecting Children's Privacy
-----------------------------

This Site is not designed nor intended to be attractive to use by children under the age of 13 (“Minors”). We do not knowingly collect PII from Minors, but we may collect information about Minors from their parents or legal guardians. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any information to us.

Cookies
-------

We use cookies to personalize our Site for you and to collect aggregate information about site usage by all of our users. A cookie is a text file that our Site transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes and to enhance the quality of your visit to our Site. The cookie assigns a random, unique number to your computer Cookies are small text files that our Site places on your browser to enable our system to recognize your computer and allow us to see how you use our site. Further general information about cookies and how they work is available at www.allaboutcookies.org. The cookies we use on our Site include:

#### A. SESSION COOKIES

These temporary cookies expire and are automatically erased whenever you close your browser window. We use session cookies to grant our users access to content and to enable actions they must be logged in to do.

#### B. PERSISTENT COOKIES

These usually have an expiration date in the distant future and remain in your browser until they expire or you manually delete them. We use persistent cookies to better understand usage patterns so we can improve the site for our customers. For example, we may use a persistent cookie to associate you with your user account or to remember that your choices on the Site, but this only works when cookies on our site are enabled.

#### C. THIRD PARTY COOKIES

We permit limited third parties to place cookies through the Site to provide us with better insights into the use of the Site or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. For example, we utilize Google Analytics to analyze usage patterns of the Site. Google Analytics generates a cookie to capture information about your use of the Site which Google uses to compile reports on website activity for us and to provide other related services. Google may use a portion of your IP address to identify their cookie, but this will not be associated with any other data held by Google.

We may also permit third party service providers to place cookies through our Site, as indicated above, to perform analytic or marketing functions where you are notified of them and you have consented to the usage. We do not control the use of such third party cookies or the resulting information and we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

Your use of our Site will be deemed to be your consent to the placement of cookies on your computer or other device. If you prefer not to receive cookies through our Site, you can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow only “trusted” websites to set them, or to accept only those cookies from those sites you are currently on. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Site and use it.

If you refuse cookies, this will limit system performance and may even cause certain features of the Site to malfunction or not to work at all.

Use of Information
------------------

The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect at the time of use. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices with respect to this Site.

We may use aggregated data (independent of any personal identifiers) for research and commercial purposes. This information includes what areas our users visit most frequently and what services they access most often. This information helps us develop better sites and services that are more useful and accessible to you.

We may use your PII for our general commercial purposes including, among other things, to conduct internal research for expansion of our products and services. We may retain service providers to carry out such research on our behalf, and in such cases we enter into specific data protection and confidentiality terms with those agents to ensure they protect your personal data to the same levels as Justworks. We may use your PII to offer our own, our affiliates’ or third-party products and services that we think you may find of interest, but only Company, its subsidiaries and its service providers involved in distributing the offers or providing the products or services will have access to your PII. Our subsidiaries and service providers will be required to use any PII we provide them only for that intended purpose.

We may use your email address to contact you to respond to your inquiries or to provide information on products or services to you, or to carry out survey or other research for the purposes of understanding your customer or user experience, improving, or expanding our products and services.

Disclosing Your Information
---------------------------

We may reveal PII about you to unaffiliated third parties: (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., gathering and analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and research assistance, providing customer service, processing payroll or taxes, etc.); or (6) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal Information, such as usage statistics of our Products, to our affiliates and third parties.

Opt-Out Rights
--------------

If you do not wish to receive offers or other notices from us in the future, you can “opt out” by contacting us at the address indicated at the end of this policy or by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in any communication you receive from us. Please be aware that you are not able to opt out of receiving communications about your account or transactions with us.

Accessing Your Information
--------------------------

You are required to provide us with accurate and up to date information. Company gives you the ability to amend your data at any time by accessing your account on our site (by clicking on the “account details” tab link on the home page), modifying the information on your account page, \[etc.\]. Any changes will affect only future uses of your PII.

Subject to any legislation which might, from time to time, oblige us to store the information for a certain period of time, we will respect your wishes to correct inaccurate information. Otherwise, we will hold your information for as long as we believe it will help us to achieve our aims as detailed in this policy.

You can ask us whether we are keeping PII about you and you can ask to receive a copy of that PII. Before sending you any PII, we will ask you to provide proof of your identity. If you are not able to provide proof of your identity, we reserve the right to refuse to send you any PII. We will respond as quickly as we can to your requests for details of PII we hold about you.

Security
--------

We have security measures in place in our physical facilities and in our computer systems, databases, and communications networks that are designed reasonably to protect information contained within our systems from loss, misuse or alteration.

No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security of your PII. You also play a role in protecting your information. Please safeguard your user name and password and do not share them with others. If we receive instructions using your log-in information we will consider that you have authorized the instructions. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security. We reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, or remove or edit content in our sole discretion.

California Privacy Rights
-------------------------

We do not share your PII with third parties for their use in directly marketing to you.

Consumers in California have the right to request disclosure of personal information collected about them, including the categories of personal information collected, the categories of sources from which personal information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting personal information, the categories of personal information disclosed for a business purpose, and the categories of third parties to whom personal information is disclosed. Subject to limitations, consumers in California may request access to or the deletion of specific pieces of personal information collected about them. Please review the “Contacting Us” section below to submit a request. Justworks does not discriminate against consumers for making requests under this section.

Please review the “Information You Provide Us,” “Information Automatically Collected,” and “Cookies” sections of this Privacy Policy for more information regarding the information collected, the sources from which it is collected, and the business purposes for collecting such information. This information may include information falling under the following categories under the California Consumer Protection Act: Geolocation Data, Identifiers, Internet or Network Information, Online Identifiers, Professional or Employment Information. Please review the “Disclosing Your Information” section of this Privacy Policy for more information regarding the circumstances in which your information may be shared with third parties.

Links to Third-Party Sites
--------------------------

When you use the Site or our service, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control. We may also allow thirds-party sites or applications to link to the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites but we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to this Site.

Do Not Track Signals
--------------------

We do not currently respond to “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that might enable users to opt out of tracking on our Site.

International Transfers
-----------------------

The PII we receive in the computers and systems of our offices and datacenters in the United States may be processed by us in the United States, where laws regarding data protection may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By using this Site and by providing any PII to the Site, all users, including without limitation users in Canada and the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States. Justworks places the utmost importance on privacy and data security controls. Justworks maintains a security program which includes technical and policy controls that are very much consistent with the requirements of GDPR.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

As our services evolve and we perceive the need or desirability of using information collected in other ways, we may from time to time amend this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect and any changes that may have been made to them. If we make material changes to this Policy we will post the revised Policy and the revised effective date on this Site. Please check back here periodically or contact us at the address listed at the end of this Policy.

Contacting Us
-------------

This site is owned and operated by Justworks, Inc . If you have any questions or suggestions with respect to this policy, or if you wish to ask us to delete, correct, or show you your information as provided above, you can write to us at Justworks, Inc., P.O. Box 7119, Church Street Station, New York, NY 10008-7119, call (888) 534-1711, or you can simply click on [\[email protected\]](https://justworks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to send us an email.

Our mission is to help entrepreneurs and businesses grow with confidence.

We do this with a simple and friendly platform, expert support from real people when it’s needed, and access to corporate-level beneﬁts that ensure people feel secure and valued.

Solutions

About

Resources

Contact Us

Newsletter

Monthly tips on running a business in your inbox.

Subscribe

Copyright © 2013-2024 Justworks, Inc. and its affiliates. All rights reserved. [Terms of Use | Privacy Policy](https://justworks.com/legal)

By accessing this site, you consent to the use of cookies and collection of personal information.
